weightwatchers.co.uk 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Weight Watchers UK

##  Weight Watchers Privacy Policy  

Your privacy and the security of your personal information are very important to us. We want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our Website and using our Internet Products. We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of those who visit our Website and use our Internet Products. This Privacy Policy governs the United Kingdom and Ireland websites operated by us (our "Website") and our Internet Products and explains how we collect your personal information on our Website or through our Internet Products, how we protect such information, and the choices you have concerning the use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. The Website is for use by residents of the United Kingdom only (excluding the Channel Islands) and Ireland only. Except as WeightWatchers.co.uk Limited ("WeightWatchers.co.uk"), Weight Watchers International, Inc. and Weight Watchers UK Limited (collectively, "we", "us", or "our" disclose in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, share, licence, trade, or rent your personal information collected on our Website or through the Internet Products to others.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website or any of our products, offerings, features, tools or resources that we provide on our Website (collectively, our "Internet Products"), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g., message board, blog, group, etc.) or through the "Community Profile" feature available on our Website, or for the privacy practices of websites that are operated or owned by third parties.

The following are links to the provisions of our Privacy Policy. For immediate access to a particular topic, click on that provision title below.

WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH OUR INTERNET PRODUCTS?

WHO OPERATES THIS WEBSITE AND WHERE ARE OUR SERVERS LOCATED?

WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH OUR INTERNET PRODUCTS?

HOW DOES OUR WEBSITE USE COOKIES?

DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN?

WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES?

DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY WHEN I LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES?

IS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT SECURE?

WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING THE COLLECTION, DISCLOSURE AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

WHAT HAPPENS TO THE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AFTER TERMINATION OF MY PAID SUBSCRIPTION?

HOW WILL I KNOW IF THERE ARE ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?

###  WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH OUR INTERNET PRODUCTS?  

We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information.

####  Personally Identifiable Information  

Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Such Personally Identifiable Information may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, birth date (primarily for eligibility purposes) and billing and credit card information. We may request Personally Identifiable Information from you when you register on our Website or subscribe to our Internet Products, or in connection with other Internet Products we may make available on our Website from time to time. In all of these cases, we will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Unless you give us permission to do so, we will not sell, share, license, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. 

You do not have to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information to visit our Website. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, you may not be able to visit all sections of our Website or use all of our Internet Products, such as subscribing to our online weight loss tools, or posting content to any Community Area on our Website. A “Community Area” means any blog, personal page, group page, message board, bulletin board, recipe swap, or similar activity. In addition, we may not be able to provide you with some of the other Internet Products dependent upon the collection of such information, such as a personalised WeightWatchers.co.uk home page.

####  Non-Personally Identifiable Information  

When you become a community user of our Website, subscribe to one of our current Internet Products, or in connection with other Internet Products we may make available on our Website from time to time, we also may collect information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (like age, profession or gender) and health information (like current weight) ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information"). Non-Personally Identifiable Information may also include user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used to help us understand who uses our Website and to improve and market our Website in general and our Internet Products in particular.

####  Information from Other Sources  

####    

We may also supplement the information we collect with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving our Website and Internet Products, to determine your preferences so that we can tailor our Website and Internet Products to your needs, and/or to study nutritional, weight loss, behavioural and fitness questions in general.

###  WHO OPERATES THIS WEBSITE AND WHERE ARE OUR SERVERS LOCATED?  

###    

This website is operated by WeightWatchers.co.uk Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales (company registration no. 04354837) and its registered office is at Third Floor, Hines Meadow, St. Cloud Way, Maidenhead, Berkshire, SL6, 8XB, United Kingdom. When you provide us with your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that this information may be stored and processed on servers located outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") and you consent to your Personally Identifiable Information being exported outside the EEA and being stored and processed at our discretion on any of our servers wherever located.

###  WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH OUR INTERNET PRODUCTS?  

We may collect information (including information that is Personally Identifiable Information) from you in different manners and at different places and times on our Website, such as when you become a community user on our Website or subscribe to one of our Internet Products. We also may collect information from you in connection with, or through, other Internet Products we may make available on our Website from time to time. The following is a description of the areas and/or manners in which we primarily collect information about you.

####  Becoming a Community User and Subscriber  

####    

In order to access certain Internet Products on our Website, such as Community Areas, weight loss tools and food database, you must first complete certain steps to become either a community user or a subscriber. During these steps, you may be required to provide us with information (including Personally Identifiable Information) such as name, postcode and email address, and, if you subscribe to one of our Internet Products, credit card and billing information. This information is used to help us understand who uses our Website, to improve our Website and our Internet Products, to contact users about requested Internet Products and/or for subscription billing purposes. It is optional for you to provide demographic information (such as profession and number of children), but providing this information is encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience on our Website.

###  HOW DOES OUR WEBSITE USE COOKIES?  

This section of our Privacy Policy contains information on what “cookies” are, the cookies used by this website, how to switch cookies off in your browser, how to specifically disable third party advertising cookies, and some useful links for further reading. If you do not see the information you were looking for, or you have any further questions about the use of cookies on this site, please email [legal@weight-watchers.co.uk](mailto:legal@weight-watchers.co.uk).

####  What Are Cookies?  

“Cookies” are small text files that are stored by your web browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Safari) on your computer’s hard drive or on your mobile phone. They allow websites to store such things as user preferences. You can think of cookies as providing a “memory” for a website, enabling it to recognise a user and respond appropriately.

Websites use both session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary cookies that expire (and are automatically erased) when you close your browser. Persistent cookies usually have an expiration date far into the future and thus stay in your browser until they expire, or until you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies for functionalities like the “Remember me on this computer” feature, which makes it possible for you to return to the site without having to log in. In addition to cookies set by the website you are visiting (first party cookies), both session and persistent cookies may be set by others (third party cookies). For example, analytics firms, social media sites and advertising networks may all set cookies when you visit other sites with which they have relationships.

###  What Types of Cookies Do We Use?  

The cookies generated when you visit our website fall into the following categories: 

**Strictly necessary cookies.** These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for. No consent is required for the use of these cookies.

For example, when you subscribe to one of our Internet Products or register as a community user, we use session cookies to signal that you are logged in so that you are able to use community or subscriber features of the Website, and persistent cookies to provide automatic login.

**Performance cookies.** These cookies collect anonymous information about how you use the Website. By using the Website or becoming a community user or subscriber, you agree that we can place these types of cookies.

We use performance cookies for web analytics, which allow us to statistically monitor how people are using our Website, to help us improve our online offerings as well as to test different design ideas for particular pages. We work with independent measurement and research companies to perform these services for us, so some of these cookies may be set by a third party company.

In particular, we use Adobe SiteCatalyst to help us track and analyze usage of our Website, using cookies and action tags. All data collected by Adobe on our behalf is owned by us and used to better understand our users and improve our Website. More information, including how to opt out of these cookies, can be found in [Adobe’s privacy policy](http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html). When you watch a video on our Website, cookies are set by the video playing technology to optimise bandwidth and help measure usage volume and delivery quality.

We may also use performance cookies to track the effectiveness of advertising purchased on third party sites, and to support our affiliate program by letting our affiliate sites know that a visitor to one of their sites later purchased a product or service on our site.

**Functionality cookies**. These cookies allow our Website to remember choices you make to improve your experience (such as your unit of measurement preferences) and to provide enhanced, more personal features (such as information about your browser and whether you have configured your Website tools), and to improve response speed and efficiency by storing certainly frequently-accessed information. By using the Website or becoming a community user or subscriber, you agree that we can place these types of cookies.

Advertising and targeting cookies. We also use cookies to assist in targeted advertising. Our Website’s advertisements may be displayed or served by a third party, and many of the advertisements you see on our Website are generated by third parties.

For example, we use DoubleClick Inc. ("DoubleClick") (owned by Google, Inc.) and Razorfish, LLC (owned by Microsoft Corp.), which employs Atlas DMT (“Atlas”) technology, to display or serve advertisements on the Website. Neither DoubleClick, Atlas nor their cookies collect Personally Identifiable Information on our Website, and we do not share Personally Identifiable Information with them without your permission. [DoubleClick's privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)describes its data collection practices and explains the way in which you can "opt-out" of certain tracking by DoubleClick. [Atlas's privacy policy ](http://atlassolutions.com/privacy-policy/)describes its data collection practices and explains the way in which you can "opt-out" of certain tracking by Atlas.

Some of our third party advertisers use their own anonymous cookies to track how many people have seen a particular ad, or to track how many people have seen it more than once. The companies that generate these cookies have their own privacy policies, and we have no access to these cookies. These third party ad cookies may be used by those third parties to anonymously target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit to our Website.

You may "opt-out" of certain tracking on our Website and other websites by various advertising companies by going to the [Your Online Choices site](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/). You can also visit the trade body representing these advertising platforms for more information: [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). They have provided a one-stop place that gathers all of the opt-out controls. Please bear in mind that there are many more networks listed on that site than those that we use on our Website.

We also set anonymous cookies on certain other sites that we advertise on. If you receive one of those cookies, we may then use it to identify you as having visited that site if you later visit our site, and will serve targeted advertising based on this information.

Other third party cookies. On some pages of our site, third parties may also set their own anonymous cookies, for the purposes of tracking the success of their application or customising the application for you. We cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in our cookies.

For example, when you share an article using a social media sharing button on our site, the social network on which you are sharing will record that you have done this.

####  How Do I Turn Cookies Off?  

You do not have to accept cookies to use our Website. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the "Help" section of the toolbar. While you are not required to accept our cookies to access our Website, if you reject cookies, certain products, offerings, features, or resources of our Website (including certain Internet Products) may not work properly and you may experience some loss of convenience.

All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings will typically be found in the “options” or “preferences” menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful; you may also use the “Help” option in your browser for more details.

Cookie settings in [Safari web](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_GB) and [ iOS](http://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)  

To turn off targeting by particular advertisers, networks or providers of analytics, you may use the opt-out functionality provided through the third-party links mentioned above.

####  How Can I Get More Information?  

If you would like to find out more about cookies and their use on the Internet, you may find the following links useful:

The IAB has provided the following website to give information specifically about privacy issues around Internet advertising: youronlinechoices.co.uk/uk. 

####  Action Tags  

"Action tags," also known as web beacons or gif tags, are a web technology used to help track website usage information, such as how many times a specific page has been viewed. Action tags are invisible to you, and any portion of our Website, including advertisements, or e-mail sent on our behalf, may contain cookies that are associated with action tags that our located on our Website. Unlike cookies, action tags are not placed on your computer.

We may select and use different third parties from time to time to track website usage through action tags on our Website and on our advertisements on other websites. For example, DoubleClick and Atlas each track anonymous website usage by setting a cookie (or reading a cookie previously placed by them) on users' computers to track the activities of users who view a web page that contains action tags. DoubleClick and Atlas may use information about your visits to this Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by one of these companies, please refer to its respective Privacy Policy. Periodically, upon our request, DoubleClick and/or Atlas may report the anonymous data that they collect on our behalf back to us for our internal use and analysis and our treatment of this anonymous data is governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

By using cookies and action tags together, we are able to gain valuable information to improve our Website and our Internet Products and measure the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns. We do not disclose any of your Personally Identifiable Information to our advertising partners through the use of cookies or action tags.

####  Social Media (Features) and Widgets  

Our Website includes social media features, buttons and widgets provided by third party social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter (collectively, the “Features”). A Feature may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. This cookie may allow the social media platform to link the foregoing data with your user profile. The Features are either hosted by the third party platform or directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the relevant platform.

####  Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider  

You can log in to our Website using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity.

####  Linking your account with third party applications and devices  

Our website offers you the option to connect your Weight Watchers account with third party applications or devices (each a “Tracker”) such as activity trackers that measure your activity level (e.g. the number of steps and distance walked, calories burned and other personal metrics). When you have purchased such a Tracker from Weight Watchers (e.g. in a Weight Watchers meeting room or online) and set up your account with the provider of the Tracker, the provider might know that this Tracker was purchased from Weight Watchers. During the set-up of your account with such provider, you might therefore be asked whether you want to connect this third party account with your Weight Watchers account. Alternatively, you will be able to connect your Weight Watchers account with your third party account in other ways, such as on the Weight Watchers website, regardless of where you have purchased your Tracker. If you connect the two accounts, the provider of your Tracker will know that you have a Weight Watchers account. At the same time, data collected via the Tracker (for example, personal activity data collected) will be transferred to us so that we can update and personalize your Weight Watchers account (for example, to display activity SmartPoints® values earned) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. You have the option to disconnect the Trackers from your Weight Watchers account at any time via our website. Please refer to the privacy policy of your Tracker provider for further details, which may include information on what specific data is collected by your third party Tracker and account.

####  Referral Programmes  

Through third party referral programme operators and others, we offer referral programmes whereby referral websites can earn commissions through the referral of subscribers or other purchasers to our Website. To track the earning of such commissions, and to determine the effectiveness of the referral programmes, the users who become subscribers to our Internet Products or purchasers through such referral websites are tracked using technologies that do not include Personally Identifiable Information (such as cookies and/or action tags). Our programme operators and the referral websites themselves can only access non-Personally Identifiable Information such as data relating to the number of impressions served, the number of transactions completed, and their resulting earnings. They cannot access our customers' personal data.

If you choose to apply to a referral website, we use the data you provide strictly for conducting business with you. We have entered into certain agreements with third party program operators for the purpose of administering our referral programmes. Should you become a referral website of ours through one of our third party programme operators, any information you provide to them is subject to their privacy policies.

####  Internet Products  

We collect information, some of which may be Personally Identifiable Information, that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to use some of our Internet Products (available either for free or on a subscription basis) such as the "My Favourites" feature, the online "POINTS&reg; Tracker" tool, the "Weight Tracker" tool and the Community Areas. We also collect information that you provide voluntarily through responses to special Internet Products such as surveys, questionnaires, self-assessment quizzes, contests and the like. Some of these Internet Products may ask you for health related information. We collect this information in order to personalise your Internet experience.

####  Public Forums and the Community Profile Feature  

We feature public forums such as those contained in the Community Areas where you and other users of our Website can communicate with one another. In addition, we offer the "Community Profile" feature of our Website to permit you to share information about yourself (including, if you elect, Personally Identifiable Information) with others. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT PROTECT YOU WHEN YOU USE OUR PUBLIC FORUMS OR PROVIDE INFORMATION (INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION) ABOUT YOURSELF THROUGH THE COMMUNITY PROFILE FEATURE OR THROUGH ANY COMMUNITY AREA AVAILABLE ON OUR WEBSITE. You should be aware that any information shared in a public forum such as a message board, blog, personal page, posting, group, bulletin board or recipe swap or through our Community Profile feature is public information and may be seen or collected by third parties (such as search engines) that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy, although the availability of personal pages or groups identified as “private” may be limited to certain permitted users. However, even information marked “private” may be viewed by our staff. Third party search engines will not collect information you designate as “private”, however once you participate in a Community Area by posting content, the content that you post (including your username) may appear in third party search engines. You should think carefully before disclosing any information in any public forum, or through the Community Profile feature, on our Website. For example, you should not select a username that includes personal information.

####  Log Files  

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information through our Internet log files, which record data such as user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website. This information may be used to analyse trends, to administer the Website, to monitor our Website's use, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to Personally Identifiable Information for these and other purposes such as personalizing your experience on our Website and evaluating our Internet Products in general.

####  Email a Friend  

####    

Through our Email a Friend tool on our Website, we will automatically send your friend a one-time email containing the information you request to be sent. If you elect to use the Email a Friend tool, we will collect from you Personally Identifiable Information about your friend which you have provided, such as your friend's name and email address. We recommend, however, that you make sure that your friend wants to receive emails from you regarding materials on our Website.

###  DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN?  

###    

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Our Website and Internet Products are not designed for or directed to individuals under the age of 18. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 18. We urge all parents or guardians to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.

###  WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?  

In general, we use the information collected on our Website and through our Internet Products to help us understand who uses our Website and Internet Products and how they are used, to personalise your online experience, to assist you in using our Internet Products, to improve our Website and Internet Products, and for subscription billing purposes, if applicable.

If you become a community user of our Website or subscribe to one of our Internet Products, we may use your information to send you a welcoming email that may confirm your user name and password. If you "opt-in" we may send you electronic newsletters, contact you about Weight Watchers products, services, information and news that may be of interest to you, and provide you with targeted feedback. If you no longer desire to receive these communications, we will provide you with the option to change your preferences. In addition, if you identify yourself to us by sending us an email with questions or comments, we may use your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to respond to your questions or comments, and we may file your questions or comments for future reference. We may also use the information collected to send you important service announcements and updates regarding our Website or Internet Products or, if you are a subscriber, about your billing account status. You will not be able to unsubscribe from these service announcements and updates as they contain important information relevant to your use of our Website and/or our Internet Products.

In addition, if you become a registered user or subscribe to one of our Internet Products after 16th March 2006, we may use your information to contact you by postal mail about Weight Watchers products, services, information and news that may be of interest to you, unless you notify us that you no longer desire to receive these communications. 

We may also use the information gathered on our Website and through our Internet Products to perform statistical analysis of user behaviour, to analyse and evaluate issues relating to nutrition, weight loss, behaviour and fitness, or to evaluate and improve our Internet Products. We may link some of this information to Personally Identifiable Information for internal purposes only or to assist you in your personal weight loss efforts.

###  WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES?  

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any information we gather from you on our Website.

####  Affiliates  

We may disclose information (including Personally Identifiable Information) about you to our Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Affiliates" means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with WeightWatchers.com, Inc., WeightWatchers.co.uk, Weight Watchers International, Inc. and Weight Watchers UK Limited, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Affiliates will be treated by those Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may share your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) with franchisees of Weight Watchers International, Inc.,, but only where we indicate to you at time of information collection that such information will be provided to a franchisee, or if we otherwise obtain your permission.

####  Laws and Legal Rights  

We may also disclose your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms & Conditions or our Subscription Agreement, or to protect the safety and/or security of our users, our Website or the general public.

####  Third Parties Generally  

We may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our Website. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our Website, the demographic breakdown of our community users of our Website, or the activities that visitors to our Website engage in while on our Website. The third parties to which we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.

####  Outside Contractors  

We may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers (collectively, "Outside Contractors") to provide specific services and products related to our Website or Internet Products , such as providing credit card processing and fraud screening, and developing applications for our Website and e-mail services. These Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on our Website, including your Personally Identifiable Information, in the course of providing products or services to us. Access to your Personally Identifiable Information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the Outside Contractors to perform their limited function for us. We also require that these contractors (i) protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (ii) not use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products or services for which we contracted.

####  Third Party Sellers  

In addition, through our Website, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or to obtain more information regarding) certain content, products or services which are sold through a person or company other than us or our Affiliates (collectively, "Third Party Sellers"). We will attempt to make it clear to you when you are dealing with a Third Party Seller by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving our Website. For example, if you see a phrase such as "powered by" or "brought to you by" followed by the name of a person or company other than WeightWatchers.co.uk, then you are likely on, or about to enter, a website hosted or operated by a person or company other than us. Third Party Sellers may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. You do not need to submit this information or purchase any products or services from Third Party Sellers to access our Website. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the Third Party Seller. This information is used by the Third Party Seller and may be subject to a different privacy policy. We do not otherwise share or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to Third Party Sellers.

####  Sale of Business  

####    

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your Personally Identifiable Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of any of us or our Affiliates provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

###  DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY WHEN I LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES?  

###  ****  

Our Website contains links to other websites not owned or operated by WeightWatchers.co.uk (for example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, you will likely be taken off our Website), including links to websites operated by franchisees of Weight Watchers International, Inc. We will attempt to make it obvious to you when you leave our Website and enter these websites by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving our Website. However, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to be aware when our Website links to other websites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Website.

###  IS THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT SECURE?  

We want your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to remain as secure as possible. We strive to provide secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers through industry-standard techniques. To help ensure the integrity and privacy of the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us via the Internet at the time you elect to become a community user or subscribe to our Internet Products, we use Secured Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in transmitting such Personally Identifiable Information over the Internet to our servers. We secure the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers located in controlled, secure environments, protected from unauthorised access, use, or alteration. Only employees who need access to your information to perform a specific task or function are granted access to such information. In addition, all WeightWatchers.co.uk employees must abide by this Privacy Policy and are kept up-to-date on security practices. Any employee who violates this Privacy Policy is subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

Notwithstanding the above commitments to protect your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

###  WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING THE COLLECTION, DISCLOSURE AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?  

###  ****  

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information for the purposes described above or as otherwise disclosed at the time we request such information from you. You must "opt-in" and give us permission to use your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose. You may change your preference and "opt-out" of receiving communications by changing that option in the My Profile feature of our Website, following the directions provided in association with the communication, or by contacting our Privacy Coordinator at the address set out below.

Users of our Website are notified when Personally Identifiable Information is being collected by third parties on our Website. We do this so you can make an informed choice as to whether you should disclose information to a third party.

###  CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?  

You can always contact us in order to (1) update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information, (2) verify what Personally Identifiable Information we maintain about you, (3) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (4) delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained about you on our systems, by accessing My Profile or contacting our Privacy Coordinator at the address set out below. Such updates, corrections, changes and deletions will not have an effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third-parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove or verify each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our systems. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. We promise that promptly after receiving your request, all Personally Identifiable Information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable.

###  WHAT HAPPENS TO THE COLLECTED PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AFTER TERMINATION OF MY PAID SUBSCRIPTION?  

###  ****  

Upon termination or cancellation of your paid subscription, you will remain a community user of our Website unless you specifically request otherwise. We will continue to store certain Personally Identifiable Information in particular to enable us to draw on these data to provide you with ongoing access to your community user account and in the event you should re-subscribe to our Website. In the event you have any objection to this, you should submit your objection to us via email to [privacy@weightwatchers.co.uk](mailto:privacy@weightwatchers.co.uk). In such case, we will delete or make anonymous your Personally Identifiable Information.

###  HOW WILL I KNOW IF THERE ARE ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?  

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If at any point we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you, at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email or otherwise, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personally Identifiable Information in the new manner. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personally Identifiable Information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Website.

###  WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?  

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Co-ordinator in any of the following ways:

Email our Privacy Coordinator at:  

Or, write to our Privacy Co-ordinator at:  
WeightWatchers.co.uk Limited  
Millennium House  
Ludlow Road  
Maidenhead, Berkshire  
SL6 2SL  
United Kingdom  
Attn: Privacy Coordinator 

Or, fax our Privacy Coordinator at:  
01628 513049  
Attn: Privacy Coordinator

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OF US PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.

(Last modified as of March 19, 2013)
